A Christmas party?
Yeah.
With me, you, Takanashi-san, and...
K-Kumin-senpai...
You still haven't given up?
Give up? She's given me the green light for friendship!
Then why not just invite her yourself?
No way! I can't do that!
Get off me!
I mean, like, it's Christmas,
so it'd be kinda suggestive...
Jeez, you're such a pain.
No, thanks.
Thought so.
I understand. You and
Takanashi-san are going on a date.
Huh?
But of course.
It is Christmas.
Hey—
Hold on, I never said I was.
We aren't going on a date.
Why not?
"Why not"?
You're dating, right?
Uh...
So you broke up?
What makes you think that?!
So you got rejected?
I'm not you, man.
Then why?
Well...
In the end, Rikka came back.
We're going to school together again.
Rikka
Our club is going strong, too.
But...
It's like nothing ever happened.
Oriental Magick Napping
Society in Summer
A kotatsu?
Master, we mustn't...
Kumin-senpai...
Where am I?!
Relax.
It's not the Dark Realm or a parallel world.
The shame!
The heat barrier was stealing my soul!
How frightening that such a device should exist in this space!
You looked pretty happy in it.
I'm being drawn in!
No! I can't fight it!
I'm in a kotatsu with Kumin-senpai...
Wh-What's this sensation on my hand?!
Huh?
Ah! The blood! The blood!
Oh, Chimaera's in there too?
Special Christmas Issue
Date
Master, be on guard!
Its allure is incredible!
Current status?
The monk and Kumin are unconscious.
Guide me.
Yes, sir!
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You looked this way
and saw me pouting with a frown ❤
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I was just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
matte miru no
That's all I really wanted ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
But the things I mumbled to myself
after "Nothing" were
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
hazukashii kara
Way too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask me what I said
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing us together
mou hajimatteta
Had already started then ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
So basically, nothing's changed since you started dating?
The Slapstick Noel... of the Shining
But our contract is now
stronger than any in history.
And so, though our daily lives have seen no transformation, concern is not necessary.
Then there's no problem.
However...
What now?
Daiki
Yuuko
Among the masses, for those under such a contract,
Daiki
Yuuko
it is typical to hold a special
ceremony on the Heilige Nacht.
Daiki
Yuuko
You want to?
Daiki
Yuuko
I am an existence separate from the masses.
Furthermore, I have no interest in the celebrations of infidels.
Then don't celebrate it.
However—
Which is it?!
Well, it depends on what you want to do.
What do you mean?
Like, do you want to be
with Togashi-kun more?
Or like, do you always want to hold hands with him?
Or like, do you want him to pat you on the head?
Sliding Vault!
Hey!
What's your problem?!
Such a vicious psychological attack...
She's such a pain...
Oh well.
I can see what you want.
A commoner such as yourself could never know the true will of the Tyrant's Eye!
Bye, then.
Wait, Agent of Light!
Idiot! Let go of that!
Okay, look.
It's almost Christmas.
Right.
Use it to your advantage.
I doubt you'd accomplish anything yourself, so we can hold a Christmas—
Party!
We're holding a Christmas party.
Huh?
Sorry, but you can't.
Can't we use the club room?
We won't go too late.
No, that's not it. The school will be closed on the 24th.
It couldn't be! A Bloody Christmas?!
Yeah, that's right.
I knew it.
Death!
Don't joke like that!
They'll take it seriously!
So we can't use the club room...
But I'd still like to have one.
Can we do it at someone's house?
Okay. We can do it at mine.
No way.
Why not?!
I'll bet your room's all messy.
You've never even seen it!
I'm thinking Togashi-kun's place would be best.
My place?
No way.
My dad said he's coming back from Jakarta.
Then what about Takanashi-san's?
Dekomori, look there!
Death!
Well...
Not happening.
I guess there's no choice!
It seems I must show you all to my stronghold!
Really? You sure?
All us high schoolers in
your house, just like that?
No problem!
Master and I shall resume our search for the source of the dark matter!
Have you been to her house, Rikka?
Once.
Dekomori's home is a fortress capable of withstanding attacks of all forms.
Fortress?
I believe it is well-suited
for our assembly.
This is Dekomori's home.
You serious?
How rich is she?
A doggy!
This breed's super expensive!
What the heck's she thinking?!
Wait...
Why me?!
Stop! Stay away from me!
Dogs really do like you, Mori Summer-chan.
Don't you mean hate?
Stop talking and help me!
Gun Twinkle!
Welcome to my castle!
Looks like... this...
really is... her home...
And she's already admitted to our school on the strength of her academics?
She's won the game of life already.
I can't accept... this reality!
Wow, Deko-chan, that's an amazing dress!
My mother picked it out for me.
A party requires the proper vestments.
Aw... I came in normal clothes.
They're more than cute enough!
Needless to say, I have also prepared mine.
I am prepared for any and all battles.
That's my master!
I brought Yuuta's too!
Why'd you do that?!
I just heard Santa Claus scream.
Master!
Hey, wait!
Oh well.
What is this place?
It's way too perfect!
Her mom was pretty too!
Are you serious?!
They'd look damn sexy on this baby!
What are you talking about?
Merry Christmas!
They had a lot of costumes, so I borrowed this one...
Doesn't look good?
No, you look great.
Yuuta.
Hm?
The day has come when I thank the world that I'm alive.
You like it that much?!
Wow, it's a fluffy sofa!
Good night!
That was fast.
Don't.
One shot!
Just one!
Where'd that damn kid go?
Your turn, huh?
Well, guess—
I asked where that kid went.
I don't know!
You don't have to wear it
if you don't want to.
She ran off with my clothes!
FAKE
Wow, talk about stubborn.
That means Takanashi-san's coming out next, right?
Well, we know what to expect.
It's her usual—
That's unexpected!
Oh, come on. A gym uniform?
What about the dress you brought?
Nibutani said this would be better.
Her, huh?
Now tell me where you hid my clothes!
Release me!
This is my stronghold!
Don't you expect to have your way so easi—
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Now I'm mad.
Nibutani.
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
Cute, right?
Why a gym uniform?!
I heard you liked it.
From who?
Touka-san.
Her, huh?
She'll pay for ruining a
high schooler's dreams.
Rikka, go get changed.
Yeah, where are my clothes?!
Okay, fine!
We'll have a contest!
A contest?
Just so you know, I'm not playing pretend with—
Fool!
This situation calls for
only one type of contest!
This.
Playing cards in such a
huge room feels unreal.
But why is she Super Millionaire?
Now give me your two cards, Super Pauper.
This environment makes it seem pretty real...
Hmph. Quite acceptable, I suppose.
There.
I'll give you these in return.
Freaking kid—
That's "Thank you very much."
Thank you very much.
It was heart-wrenching to watch.
I need to get back at her somehow.
Yes! Here it is!
Time to rise in revolt!
I'll drag the fat and plump Deko the Millionaire down from that pedestal!
Here, Deko-chan!
Let's see!
Anyway, let's start.
The Super Pauper plays first—
I hope you're ready!
Keep thinking you've won everything
and the rug'll be pulled from under you!
A revolution?!
What?!
Well?
Please, stop!
Don't underestimate the power of the peop—
She quelled it?!
Is that even possible?
Hey, what was that for?!
I just happened to have them.
Good work!
Didn't I already say I'd drag her down?!
FAKE
You did?
Go nap on that sofa if you aren't gonna listen!
It's not really a game anymore...
Don't be so mad, Mori Summer-chan!
Right, Rikka?
Rikka?
Where'd she wander off to?
Yuuta.
Rikka.
Rikka?!
What are you doing up there?!
Hey, your face is kinda red...
No way!
Ow...
Yuuta!
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't tell me you're...
Looks like this is what caused it.
She ate at least three of them.
Looks like you really can get drunk off this.
Hey, come on!
Be a good girl and sit down!
Yuuta! An illusionist, over there!
The heavens...
Enough, just go to sleep.
Yuuta...
What is it?
You!
Give me back my master!
Hey, don't tell me you had some too...
Mjollnir Hammer!
Ow, ow, ow. Could you quit it?
You're so unfair!
Toying around with Master's feelings all you want!
Master is a gallant and noble soul!
You should be more grateful!
I'm not toying around with her...
Yes, you are!
Ow...
Master speaks of nothing but you!
About how you smiled,
got mad, or looked away!
Why don't you try listening to all that?!
Hey! What does that
have to do with anything?!
Dekomori, move.
Yuuta's resolve as the Dark Flame Master is too weak.
Huh?
If the prophecies of the Tyrant's Eye should
guide the present reality into its destined future,
the inevitable final battle of the world shall come to pass upon this plane.
Seems legit, but I have no idea what you're talking about!
Regardless, you frustrate me, Yuuta!
Master!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Vanishment, this world!
You're not getting away.
Mjollnir Lightning!
You trying to kill me?!
Avalon Smasher!
Mjollnir Tornado!
Two-on-one's no fair!
I feel sick...
Huh?
What are you doing?
The world is spinning...
Yeah, yeah, just lie down.
Sorry.
I just couldn't find the right moment.
I told you I'd find a natural way to
get you two alone together, didn't I?
Unnecessary.
You sure?
The Tyrant's Eye sees all. There is no need.
Well, it is hard for a girl to ask.
I understand—
You've experienced it before?!
You jumped on fast!
No, I haven't.
I was just saying it's hard for a girl to ask.
So I think Christmas is a perfect time.
I see.
Don't you get this picture in your
head when you think of Christmas?
A bloody massacre!
What kind of picture is that?
I'm talking about couples.
A guy and girl together.
A bloody massacre!
Well, I guess for some couples—
No! I'm talking about couples holding hands and kissing!
I'm sure Togashi-kun
thinks about it a lot too.
He doesn't.
Really?
I swear on the Tyrant's Eye.
Done changing?
Yeah, you can come in.
How's she doing?
She's calmed down a little.
Now she's asleep.
I see.
Maybe I should take her home.
Huh?
She lives a floor above me, after all.
Yeah, I guess.
Well, sorry about this.
Please handle the rest.
Sure.
What was that?
Doesn't matter.
You go wake Kumin-senpai up—
Where's Master?
She went home with Togashi-kun.
I won't let him defeat Master!
I'll defend her—
Yeah, yeah. Now let's go back in.
Release me! Release me!
What's the matter with you?
Huh?
You've been manhandling me all the time lately.
I've been attacking you with all my might.
What? Now you're mad at me?
You used to be more serious!
You chased me like there was no tomorrow!
But...
First Master, and now you...
Oh, give me a break!
Don't cry.
Then take me to Master!
Why do I have to do that?
We can still make it...
Hey, Rikka...
What?
I bought these for Christmas.
I thought they might go to waste because of the party, but...
Yuuta...
Want to go?
If you're feeling okay, that is.
I'm fine.
Yuuta, look! Yuuta!
Yeah, yeah.
So pretty...
First time on a tour boat?
Yeah.
What about you?
Only when I was a kid.
Oh, that's the district we live in.
Oh! A barrier is already erected!
Something's wrong with that district over there.
Has the seal been released?!
Man, you never change.
Huh?
You know...
I've been thinking, and...
Huh?
Um...
About us.
And, like...
I don't know what we should do, but...
I don't think we need to rush.
The same goes for eighth-grade syndrome.
We can just be ourselves, go with the flow, and see where it takes us.
So, like...
It's getting cold out here. Why don't we go inside?
Okay.
Wait right there!
Dekomori?
I restrained myself and watched, but what was that?!
Hey, are you still...
Surely you jest!
I can't leave Master in your hands!
I told you, stop it!
Sorry.
You guys!
What are you doing here?
Deko-chan insisted, so...
We agreed to just watch from the sidelines, but...
Hey, now...
I said we're sorry.
Give Master back.
Mjollnir Hammer!
Rikka!
Leave it to me!
I'll protect you, Yuuta—
You okay?
Yeah.
Wait.
What was that kissing soun—
Wh-What are you doing?!
I should be asking you!
Freaking kid, taking my first kiss!
And so, Christmas passed, but my relationship with Rikka didn't change much.
I don't care! Get off me!
You're the one on top!
And there wasn't the slightest sign that
Kumin-senpai and Isshiki's was going anywhere.
You just looked at me with lewd eyes!
No, that was you!
Trying to blame it on me?!
Hey, get away from me!
As for these two...
You get away from me!
...a new fl—
Don't call it a flag!
I'm home.
Onii-chan
But, well...
That might be for the best.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, that reminds me.
The world didn't end.
To Be Continued
... Or Not?
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?