kono sekai no chiisana basho de
On that day that I came and I first found you
kimi no sugata wo mitsuketa ano hi
In a tiny place in this wide world
kaze wo ukete waratteita ne
The wind blew past you, and you were laughing
watashi no kokoro ga somatteita
In a moment it was burned forever in my heart
dore dake chikaku ni itatte
No matter how close I stay by you
omoi ga tsutawaru wake ja nai ne
My feelings still might never be able to reach you
dore dake hanaretemo
No matter how far apart we are
kono omoi kawaranai yo
These feelings I have will never change
unmei toka eien toka
Destiny and eternity
kowashite demo soba ni iru
I'll be by your side even if you destroy them
ashita yori mo ima daisuki da yo
I love this moment more than what tomorrow might bring
owari nante konai dakara motto...
The end will never come, so, please...
utsukushisa mo sutekisa mo
Everything wonderful and everything beautiful
nakute ii kara
Can just go away
kuruoshii hodo ni aisasete
I want to love you so much that it drives me insane
ano hi no kotoba wasurenai
I'll never forget your words on that day
wasurerarenai kimi he
I'll never be able to forget you
todoite hoshii
I want you to know how I feel
Oh, nice to meet you!
My name is Tsuyuri Kumin.
My last name is written "May 7th," but it's read "Tsuyuri."
Despite that, my birthday is in October.
Oh well.
My hobby is sleeping.
I love napping.
It's great!
Nothing beats a good nap!
Sleeping After School Beauty
That's why I made the Napping Club.
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
The actual name is more wordy and complicated, but it's still the Napping Club.
We have first-year members too.
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
Good morning!
I come here every day for club activities.
Which, of course, includes napping.
These are my pillows.
I use a different pillow depending on the season, weather, and my mood.
I can't imagine ever napping without one.
Next, I choose a spot to take my nap.
Whether the windows are open or closed is important.
While it's best to nap with a fresh breeze,
if it's too strong, you could catch a cold.
You also need to consider the sun.
If you get too much sunlight, you might dream about being trapped in an inferno!
You can never be too careful.
Good night!
What's up?
Huh? You're the only one here, Senpai?
Yep! Just me.
This is Togashi Yuuta-kun.
He's the first-year
who contributed the most to forming the club.
But for some reason, he doesn't seem very interested in participating.
Togashi-kun! Why don't you take a nap?
I'll lend you a pillow.
No, I'm good.
This is Dekomori Sanae-chan.
She's still a third-year in middle school,
but she always comes to our club meetings.
Deko-chan! Here's your milk!
Strawberry
Milk
That milk is tainted with blood!
It's strawberry-flavored!
She doesn't like milk very much.
Nevertheless, she makes sure to drink some every day so she can grow taller.
The flavor should make it easier!
I hope so...
Blood!
It tastes like blood!
Like hell it does!
Togashi-kun always makes remarks like that.
He's constantly playing the straight man.
It must be a lot of work.
Man, I'm exhausted.
I'll never understand why sports clubs care so much about seniority.
This is Nibutani Shinka-chan.
Not only is she a first-year class rep,
she's really smart and popular too!
You dare show yourself, Fake Mori Summer?
Don't call me that!
She shows her true colors here, though.
Are you trying to kill me?!
She and Deko-chan get along very well.
M-Master!
Good morning!
And this is Takanashi Rikka-chan.
Apparently, she has mysterious powers
that allow her to see dark beings.
Being with her is a lot of fun!
Is there something here?
I'm sensing traces of a dark being who has crossed the Horizon to get to this realm.
There!
Oh! Look, there's a strain!
That's been there since yesterday.
And stop encouraging her, Senpai.
Togashi-kun never plays along.
I get the feeling he really wants to, though.
It's my duty as a servant to protect my master!
Mjollnir Hammer—
Try being quiet for a change.
Unhand me!
Unhand me at once!
Yuuta! Unleash the powers of darkness!
Prepare for battle!
Hell no!
Hurry! Before it's too late!
Every day is fun and full of life, just like this.
There's nothing wrong!
But I think I'm the only one who's taken a nap since the club was founded.
Come, Dark Flame Master!
I told you not to call me that!
Well, that's okay.
Which is it?!
I have no choice.
Schwarzsechs Prototype Mark II!
Will you quit it?!
And that name is way too long!
To be continued
At the break (Doom!) of the dark dawn (Gloom!)
shikkoku no (ha) akatsuki ni (zetsu)
Cut through the heavens and cleave apart the world (Slash!)
kokuu wo kirisaite yo wo ugate (zan)
Now it's time to part (Ruin!) Here's a flower for your soul (Death!)
saa owakare da (metsu) hana wo tamukeyou (sou)
rinpyo-to-sha-kaijin rettsu go-!
Rin Pyou Tou Sha Kai Jin Let's Go!
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
...are you ready now?
...kakugo wa ii ka?
Quiver, and be still!
furuete nemure
Ugh... Not that dream again
uu... mata ano yume ka
My head is pounding like it might split in two
atama ga wareteshimaisou da
koyoi mangetsu ga uruwashii
The full moon tonight is magnificent
The eye which reflects all truth begins to throb
shinjitsu wo utsusu hitomi ga uzukidasu
(Dance! Dance! Jaoushingan!)
(odore odore jaoushingan)
I'm not off guard, I'm just bored, you see?
yudan de wa nai taikutsu na no sa
I've long forgotten all the gods to which you pray
inoru kami nado tou ni wasureta
fua~aa~aa saa utageja
Fwaa-aa-aah! Now let us feast!
(In Heaven and on Earth I alone am honored! Yay!)
(tenjoutenge yuigadokuson washo-i)
watashi nara koko ni iruzo
You know, I'm right here for you
But don't get too close, I can't control it!
dakedo chikadzukuna seigyo dekinai...
ten ga naite umi ga hoe watashi ga saikyou da
The Heavens cry, the Seas howl, I'm the strongest now!
Why don't you get it?
naze kidzukanai?
That's the problem with you foolish humans!
kore dakara ningen wa...
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
Are you ready now?
kakugo wa ii ka!