kono sekai no chiisana basho de
On that day that I came and I first found you
kimi no sugata wo mitsuketa ano hi
In a tiny place in this wide world
kaze wo ukete waratteita ne
The wind blew past you, and you were laughing
watashi no kokoro ga somatteita
In a moment it was burned forever in my heart
dore dake chikaku ni itatte
No matter how close I stay by you
omoi ga tsutawaru wake ja nai ne
My feelings still might never be able to reach you
dore dake hanaretemo
No matter how far apart we are
kono omoi kawaranai yo
These feelings I have will never change
unmei toka eien toka
Destiny and eternity
kowashite demo soba ni iru
I'll be by your side even if you destroy them
ashita yori mo ima daisuki da yo
I love this moment more than what tomorrow might bring
owari nante konai dakara motto...
The end will never come, so, please...
utsukushisa mo sutekisa mo
Everything wonderful and everything beautiful
nakute ii kara
Can just go away
kuruoshii hodo ni aisasete
I want to love you so much that it drives me insane
ano hi no kotoba wasurenai
I'll never forget your words on that day
wasurerarenai kimi he
I'll never be able to forget you
todoite hoshii
I want you to know how I feel
My name is Togashi Kuzuha.
My Brother
This is a story from when my brother was in eighth grade and still acted weird.
I'm full!
Onii-chan, your dinner's getting cold.
Forgive me, my dear sister,
but I cannot consume this dish.
Huh?
As the Dark Flame Master, it is imperative that I train my mind.
In order to hone my powers of concentration,
I must abstain from eating.
Onii-chan?
I shall now perform six hours of meditation.
I shall speak to no one during this time.
I'm home.
Yuuta?
What's going on?
I wanna play too!
Hey, that hurts!
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
What in the world are you doing?
I'm trying to meditate here!
I need to concentrate on—
I must recall my dark soul from the shadows.
What are you talking about?
Oh, is this part of that Yu-Hel-something card game that you kids love so much?
N-No!
Don't worry. I can go by myself.
No. He's going with you.
What's taking him so long?
I'm ready.
Is the Moon out?
Huh?
I asked if the Moon is out.
Yeah, it should be.
Then I'll use these.
The air clings to my skin.
They must be close.
Oh, Kuzuha-chan?
Oh, Mika-chan!
Where are you going?
Oh, I was just on my way to the store to pick up some stationery!
Let's go together!
Halt, my dear sister.
Sister?
Are you Kuzuha-chan's brother?
Indeed.
However, we know not if we are, in fact, siblings.
There was a battle on the other side of the Horizon, after all.
Battle?
He kind of likes to play around like this.
He's so cool.
He's so cool!
What?!
Let's roll.
Okay!
Mika-chan?
Mika-chan!
For a moment,
I thought that maybe, just maybe, Onii-chan might actually be cool.
Keep up the good work.
But on second thought,
I think I like his normal side more.
To be continued
At the break (Doom!) of the dark dawn (Gloom!)
shikkoku no (ha) akatsuki ni (zetsu)
Cut through the heavens and cleave apart the world (Slash!)
kokuu wo kirisaite yo wo ugate (zan)
Now it's time to part (Ruin!) Here's a flower for your soul (Death!)
saa owakare da (metsu) hana wo tamukeyou (sou)
rinpyo-to-sha-kaijin rettsu go-!
Rin Pyou Tou Sha Kai Jin Let's Go!
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
...are you ready now?
...kakugo wa ii ka?
Quiver, and be still!
furuete nemure
Ugh... Not that dream again
uu... mata ano yume ka
My head is pounding like it might split in two
atama ga wareteshimaisou da
koyoi mangetsu ga uruwashii
The full moon tonight is magnificent
The eye which reflects all truth begins to throb
shinjitsu wo utsusu hitomi ga uzukidasu
(Dance! Dance! Jaoushingan!)
(odore odore jaoushingan)
I'm not off guard, I'm just bored, you see?
yudan de wa nai taikutsu na no sa
I've long forgotten all the gods to which you pray
inoru kami nado tou ni wasureta
fua~aa~aa saa utageja
Fwaa-aa-aah! Now let us feast!
(In Heaven and on Earth I alone am honored! Yay!)
(tenjoutenge yuigadokuson washo-i)
watashi nara koko ni iruzo
You know, I'm right here for you
But don't get too close, I can't control it!
dakedo chikadzukuna seigyo dekinai...
ten ga naite umi ga hoe watashi ga saikyou da
The Heavens cry, the Seas howl, I'm the strongest now!
Why don't you get it?
naze kidzukanai?
That's the problem with you foolish humans!
kore dakara ningen wa...
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
Are you ready now?
kakugo wa ii ka!